<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Bestiality / Zoophilia Paths -->
  <Luxandra_Letter_FeralDevotion_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Feral Devotion</Luxandra_Letter_FeralDevotion_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_FeralDevotion_AnimalMother_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s miracle. By guiding your human seed into the wild beasts of the world, your colony has shattered the boundaries of standard flesh to prove true to its carnal doctrine. She rewards your raw fidelity with a grand ecstasy.</Luxandra_Letter_FeralDevotion_AnimalMother_Desc>
  <Luxandra_Letter_FeralDevotion_HumanMother_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn. By embracing the wild, beastial lineage of the father, your colony has proven true to its carnal doctrine. She rewards your raw fidelity.</Luxandra_Letter_FeralDevotion_HumanMother_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_PrimalContamination_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Primal Contamination</Luxandra_Letter_PrimalContamination_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_PrimalContamination_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s unnatural newborn with profound disdain. A man of your colony has willingly surrendered his humanity to an animal, leaving a stain of bestial violation upon your community. A heavy fog descends upon your minds, dragging your consciousness down to match the beast you so eagerly defiled.</Luxandra_Letter_PrimalContamination_Desc>
  <Luxandra_Letter_PrimalContamination_HumanMother_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn with profound disdain. An bestial violation has stained your community. A heavy fog descends upon your minds, dragging your consciousness down to match the beast you so eagerly defiled.</Luxandra_Letter_PrimalContamination_HumanMother_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_DomesticDefiance_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Domestic Defiance</Luxandra_Letter_DomesticDefiance_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_DomesticDefiance_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn and finds it lacking. You have defaulted to sterile, civilized normalcy. To break your domestic complacency, she commands the wild to correct your path.</Luxandra_Letter_DomesticDefiance_Desc>

  <!-- Prostitution / Whore Paths -->
  <Luxandra_Letter_CommercialFertility_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Commercial Fertility</Luxandra_Letter_CommercialFertility_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_CommercialFertility_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn. By generating life through the sacred transactional exchange of the flesh, your colony honors her carnal marketplace. She grants a swelling gift of physical beauty across your colonists, ensuring they remain happy and pleasing to look upon.</Luxandra_Letter_CommercialFertility_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_InsularHoarding_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Insular Hoarding</Luxandra_Letter_InsularHoarding_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_InsularHoarding_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn with sharp irritation. You waste your seed on insular, domestic comfort rather than using your bodies to populate and subvert the neighboring factions. To punish your selfish prudeness and break your hoarders' mentality, a deviant tribal horde descends to forcibly open your gates.</Luxandra_Letter_InsularHoarding_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_UntrackedContagion_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Untracked Contagion</Luxandra_Letter_UntrackedContagion_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_UntrackedContagion_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn with disgust. You have allowed your colony's lineage to be compromised by a commercialized union of unknown origin and health. To correct this careless breeding, she unleashes a burning fever across your community.</Luxandra_Letter_UntrackedContagion_Desc>

  <!-- Rape / Non-Consent Paths -->
  <Luxandra_Letter_SovereignDominion_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Sovereign Dominion</Luxandra_Letter_SovereignDominion_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_SovereignDominion_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn. The product of absolute subjection and forceful conquest validates your creed of total authority. Your dominance is rewarded.</Luxandra_Letter_SovereignDominion_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_FracturedOrder_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Fractured Order</Luxandra_Letter_FracturedOrder_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_FracturedOrder_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn. A violent, undisciplined acts has fractured your civilized vows. She unleashes the White Rain to show you what it truly means to lose control over your instincts.</Luxandra_Letter_FracturedOrder_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_InsipidConsent_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Insipid Consent</Luxandra_Letter_InsipidConsent_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_InsipidConsent_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn and rejects it. Your colonists chose soft, mutual compromise over absolute dominion. She sends a horde of true deviants to ruthlessly remind what your duty was.</Luxandra_Letter_InsipidConsent_Desc>

  <!-- Incest Paths -->
  <Luxandra_Letter_SacredLineage_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Sacred Lineage</Luxandra_Letter_SacredLineage_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_SacredLineage_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn. By weaving your family's blood back into itself, you have rejected the chaotic diluting of the outside world to preserve a pure, concentrated form.</Luxandra_Letter_SacredLineage_Desc>

 <Luxandra_Letter_ForbiddenBlood_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Forbidden Blood</Luxandra_Letter_ForbiddenBlood_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_ForbiddenBlood_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn with disgust. By bringing forth a child born of the forbidden and overlapping bloodlines you have crossed the one line you vowed to never cross. In her displeasure, she has reached into the minds of the offenders and extinguished their fires. The thought of intimacy now brings only a sickening, ash-like numbness. You will regret ever allowing your base desires to cross that forbidden line.</Luxandra_Letter_ForbiddenBlood_Desc>

  <Luxandra_Letter_ExogamousBetrayal_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Exogamous Betrayal</Luxandra_Letter_ExogamousBetrayal_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_ExogamousBetrayal_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn and rejects it. You were explicitly commanded to breed within the sacred bloodline, yet you have chosen to look outward. Luxandra is thoroughly unamused by your domestic defiance. If you will not follow willingly, she will force your hands. A suffocating pressure fills the minds of your colonists, turning their blood to liquid fire and sending their desires into a desperate frenzy.</Luxandra_Letter_ExogamousBetrayal_Desc>
  

  <!-- Default Pure Path -->
  <Luxandra_Letter_SanctifiedUnion_Title>Luxandra's Appraisal: Sanctified Union</Luxandra_Letter_SanctifiedUnion_Title>
  <Luxandra_Letter_SanctifiedUnion_Desc>Luxandra has appraised the birth of {0}'s newborn. Your commitment to your community's continuity is recognized. She blesses your dedication to a pure and disciplined order.</Luxandra_Letter_SanctifiedUnion_Desc>

</LanguageData>